http://www.equestriansingles.com/privacy_policy

Privacy Policy
This document represents a legal document that serves as our Privacy Policy. It governs the privacy terms of our Service. Our Privacy Policy is part of our Legal Terms. Capitalized terms, unless otherwise defined below, have the meaning specified within the Definitions section our Terms of Service.
The last update to our Privacy Policy was posted on May 15, 2019. EquestrianSingles.com follows all legal requirements to protect your privacy. Our Privacy Policy is a legal statement that explains how we may collect information from you, how we may share your information, and how you can limit our sharing of your information.
We break up the types of information you share into Non Personal Information and Personally Identifiable Information. "Non Personal Information" is information that is not personally identifiable to you and that we automatically collect when you access our Service with a web browser. "Personally Identifiable Information" is non-public information that is personally identifiable to you and obtained in order for us to provide you within access to certain features of our Service. Personally Identifiable Information may include information such as your email address, physical location, and other related information that you provide to us or that we obtain about you. It may also include any pictures that upload when using our Service.
Information We Collect:
Generally, you control the amount and type of information you provide to EquestrianSingles.com when using our Service. As a Visitor, you can browse our Website to find out more about our Service. You are not required to provide us with any Personally Identifiable Information as a Visitor. However, if register as a Member to use our Service, you must provide Personally Identifiable Information to EquestrianSingles.com in order for us to provide you with certain features our Service. As a Member, we collect your Personally Identifiable Information in the following ways:
At Member Registration: When you register for membership, we collect your email address so that we can communicate with you about our Service.Participation in Our Service: As a Member participating in our Service, you may disclose Personally Identifiable Information such as personal information about yourself or images of yourself. You should take great care in what you disclose and in what images you may upload to protect your privacy as you see fit. We don’t have a duty to review what you submit to make sure that no identifiers are present.At Subscription: When you purchase a Subscription for our Service, we collect your Payment Method and other billing information so that we can charge you for your Subscription. Online Forms: There are many online forms used in our Service. The information you enter into these online forms may contain Personally Identifiable Information.Computer Information Collected: When you use our Service, EquestrianSingles.com automatically collects certain computer information by the interaction of your mobile phone or web browser with our Service. Such information is typically considered Non Personal Information.
EquestrianSingles.com also collects the following:
Cookies: Our Service uses “Cookies” to identify the areas of our Service that you have visited. A Cookie is a small piece of data stored on your computer or mobile device by your web browser. We use Cookies to personalize the Content that you see on our Service. Most web browsers can be set to disable the use of Cookies. However, if you disable Cookies, you may not be able to access functionality on our Service correctly or at all. We never place Personally Identifiable Information in Cookies.Web Beacons: We may also use a technology called, web beacons, to collect general information about your use of our Service and your use of special promotions or newsletters. The information we collect by Web Beacons allows us to statistically monitor the number of people that open our emails. Our Web Beacons are not used to track your activity outside of our Service. We do not link Non Personal Information from Web Beacons to Personally Identifiable Information without your permission.Automatic Information: We automatically receive information from your web browser or mobile device. This information includes the name of the Service from which you entered our Service, if any, as well as the name of the Service to which you’re headed when you leave our Service. This information also includes the IP address of your computer/proxy server that you use to access the Internet, your Internet Service provider name, web browser type, type of mobile device, and computer operating system. We use all of this information to analyze trends among our Users to help improve our Service.“Do Not Track/Follow” Settings: In compliance with applicable laws, EquestrianSingles.com wants you to know that our Website does not currently honor “do not track” or “do not follow” settings as your web browser may allow, nor do we have any liability for not doing so. If we change our policy in the future, it will be reflected here in an update to our Privacy Policy.
How We Use Your Information
EquestrianSingles.com uses the information we receive from you as follows:
Providing and Improving Our Service: EquestrianSingles.com may use the Personally Identifiable information you provide to us along with any computer information we receive to provide our Service to you as well as to make improvements to it.Communications and Email Alerts: When EquestrianSingles.com communicates with you about our Service, we will use the
email address you provided when registering as a Member. We may also send you service alerts regarding your use of our
Service. Finally, we may also send you emails with promotional information about EquestrianSingles.com, unless you have opted
out of receiving such information. You can change contact preferences at any time through your account. While you can optout
of promotional messages, you cannot opt-out of receiving service alerts.Sharing Information with Affiliates and Other Third Parties: EquestrianSingles.com does not sell, rent, or otherwise
provide your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties for marketing purposes. However, we may use non-personal
information regarding your use of our Website for data aggregation purposes which might be sold to other parties at our
discretion. Any such data aggregation would not contain any of your Personally Identifiable Information. We may provide
your Personally Identifiable Information to affiliates that provide services to EquestrianSingles.com with regards to our Service
(i.e. payment processors, webhosting companies, etc.); such affiliates will only receive information necessary to provide the
respective services and will be bound by confidentiality agreements limiting the use of such information.Community Discussion Boards: Our Service may offer the capability for Users to communicate with each other through
online Community Discussion Boards. EquestrianSingles.com does not filter or monitor what is posted on such discussion boards.
If you chose to post on these discussion boards, you should use care when exposing any Personally Identifiable Information as
such information is not protected by our Privacy Policy nor are we liable should you choose to disclose Personally Identifiable
Information through such postings.Legally Required Releases of Information: EquestrianSingles.com may be legally required to disclose your Personally
Identifiable Information, if such disclosure is (a) required by subpoena, law, or other legal process; (b) necessary to assist law
enforcement officials or government enforcement agencies; (c) necessary to investigate violations of or otherwise enforce our
Legal Terms; (d) necessary to protect us from legal action or claims from third parties including you and/or other Members;
and/or (e) necessary to protect the legal rights, personal/real property, or personal safety of EquestrianSingles.com, our Users,
employees, and affiliates.Disclosures to Successors: If EquestrianSingles.com is acquired or merges, in whole or in part, with another business that would
become responsible for providing the Service to you, we retain the right to transfer your Personally Identifiable Information
to the new business. The new business would retain the right to use your Personally Identifiable Information according to the
terms of this Privacy Policy as well as to any changes to this Privacy Policy as instituted by the new business.Changing Your Information: You may change your Personally Identifiable Information at any time using the Account &
Settings Tab on our Service.Protecting Your Child’s Privacy: We want to protect your Child’s privacy. Even though our Service is not designed for use by a
Child, we realize that a Child may attempt to access our Website. We do not knowing collect Personally Identifiable Information
from a Child. If you are a parent or guardian and believe your Child is using our Website, please contact us. We may ask for
proof of identification before we remove any information to prevent malicious removal of account information. If we discover
on our own that a Child is accessing our Website, we will delete the information as soon as we discover it, we will not use the
information for any purpose, and we will not disclose the information to third parties. You acknowledge that we do not verify
the age of our Users nor do we have any liability to do so. If you are a Child, please do not access our Website.Protecting the Privacy Rights of Third Parties: We believe in everyone’s right to privacy. If any postings you make to our
Service contain information about third parties, you need to make sure you have permission to include them in your posting.
While we are not legally liable for the actions of our Users, we will remove any postings for which we are notified that such
postings violate the privacy rights of others.Links to Other Websites: Our Service may contain links to other websites. You agree that EquestrianSingles.com has no control
over such websites and that such websites are NOT subject to this Privacy Policy. These websites may have their own privacy
policies and other legal documents. It is your sole responsibility to verify the privacy policies and other legal documents of
such websites to see how they treat your personal information. You acknowledge that your use and access of these websites is
solely at your own risk.Our Email Policy: EquestrianSingles.com and our affiliates fully comply with international laws regarding SPAM. You can always
opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from EquestrianSingles.com and/or our affiliates. We agree that we will not
sell, rent, or trade your email address to any unaffiliated third-party without your permission.Our Security Policy: EquestrianSingles.com has constructed our Service using industry standard encryption and authentication
tools to protect your Personally Identifiable Information. When we collect your Personally Identifiable Information through our
Service, we encrypt this information and attempt to prevent unauthorized access to it by using industry standard technologies,
such as encryption software, routers and firewalls. Unfortunately, due to the nature of the Internet, we cannot completely
guarantee that your Personally Identifiable Information is completely protected. We strongly urge you to protect any password
you may have for our Service and to not share it with anyone. You should always log out of our Service when not in use,
especially if you are sharing a computer or mobile device with someone else or are using a public computer.Privacy Policy Updates: EquestrianSingles.com reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. You should review this Privacy Policy frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. We will also change the "Last Updated" date at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Any changes we make to our Privacy Policy are effective as of this Last Updated date and replace any prior Privacy Policies.Changing Your Information: You may change your email address or other Personally Identifiable Information at any time using the account management features found on our Service.Questions About Our Privacy Practices or This Privacy Policy: If you have any questions about our Privacy Practices or this Policy, please contact us by email at privacy@EquestrianSingles.com.
About UsTerms Of ServicePrivacy PolicyFrequently Asked Questions
EquestrianSingles.com © 2002-2020 All Rights Reserved.
EquestrianSingles® does not conduct background checks on the members or subscribers of this website.
v._6c719cc
